Hello, I'm sorry for the wait.
This is your chicken inasal.
Please enjoy.
I think they got the order wrong.
They got served before us.
Oh, you're right.
I think our food went over there.
Hi, guys. Did you order fish?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Sorry for the wait.
Didn't they come in after us as well?
They just got the fish, too!
[The Frustration Is Real]
What if our food isn't coming?
Is that all we're getting?
Right, I think something went wrong
with our order.
Should we ask?
[The Frustration is Real]
Excuse me?
Yes?
Are we finished the dish?
- Fish and one chicken.
- And inasal.
Okay, I'm so sorry for the wait.
Let me get that.
Guys!
The fish Chef served to Table 1
should've gone to Table 5.
Eh? Why?
Both Tables 6 and 5 have inasal,
but Table 5 should get it first.
- Six, seven, six.
- They ordered first, yeah.
Huh? There are two.
Chef! Oh no, he went out...
- Okay! Yeah!
- Yeah!
Hands, hands, hands, hands.
Chef already served the fish.
Oh my gosh.
I'll put the inasal.
Okay, please get it ready.
- Okay, enjoy!
- Thank you!
- Chef!
- What?
Chef, one more inasal.
Okay.
The one you served was for another table.
They're the ones who were waiting for so long.
No, but I asked them, "Did you order fish?"
And they said, "Yes."
Yeah, they also ordered one fish.
- Okay, inasal, one.
- Okay, one.
Disaster!
Okay, let's make the inasal on the house.
- Yes.
- Okay, yes.
Sorry about the inasal.
Sorry.
We will serve it, and it's going to be free.
The inasal.
- So, again, sorry for the delay, sir.
- How long should we wait?
Maybe five to seven minutes?
Would that be okay?
- Should we wait?
- It takes 7 minutes.
Should we cancel the fish?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Can we cancel the fish?
Ah, you want to cancel the fish?
Yes, because it takes too long.
Okay, okay.
Again, I am so sorry.
- Full.
- Oh, yeah.
Thank you. Thank you for your patience.
Thank you.
- Okay, this table canceled the...
- Fish?
- Fish. They're only waiting for the inasal.
- Inasal.
- I told them it's free.
- Okay, okay.
Sorry, I need to know...
Later, I'll figure out the table numbers.
I'm sorry.
I was the one
who served the fish to that table.
Oh, it's okay.
Later, during the break,
- let's sort out the table numbers and all.
- Yeah.
Can you prepare two inasal plates? And then...
- I'll do it.
- Yeah.
Okay, 30 seconds.
Okay. Alright!
Inasal, coming, coming.
You carry one, I carry one.
Go, go, go.
Oh! It's here, it's here!
- It's finally here.
- Hey.
Hey guys, oh my God,
we're so sorry for the delay.
We're so sorry.
Thank you.
We're really sorry.
- Can we take this, sir?
- Yes.
Okay, thank you.
- Enjoy your meal!
- Thank you.
- Enjoy, guys!
- Yes.
- So sorry for the delay.
- We're so sorry.
Okay, thank you.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Okay.
Oh no, what do we do?
Okay.
The inasal was actually worth the wait.
- Thank God.
- Not really!
Just kidding. That took too long, Chef!
It's delicious, though.
Oh my gosh! They've been waiting all day!
One whole day.
I'm sorry!
Just kidding!
[Chicken Inasal]
[After a long wait]
It's good.
It's delicious, so delicious.
The onion cuts through all the greasiness.
- It's good, right?
- It's good!
Thank you.
Wow, it's really good.
- It's really good.
- Everything's really good.
It tastes like marinated grilled ribs.
- Right?
- It's good.
If I had two stomachs,
I would've ordered everything.
Everything looks so good.
That was good.
Shall we go?
- Hi, so you're checking out?
- The food was good.
Thank you very much
for trying out our restaurant.
Thank you for waiting.
This is for you.
- Please. Have one, one, one, one.
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Photo.
Okay!
Thank you!
One...
One, two, three!
- Thank you.
- Take care!
- Bye-bye!
- Thank you.
Thank you.
- Bye-bye!
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
[Open]
[Closed]
[Break Time]
I think we're hungry.
- Let's go, let's cook!
- Okay, let's cook, let's cook.
[Kumusta]
[One Humble Plate]
It's giving...
sexy chef.
Sexy chef!
[Sexy Chef]
- What is?
- Kimchigang.
[Kimchigang]
Kimchigang?
- Yes.
- Is it like kimchi sinigang?
- Yes, kimchigang.
- Something like that?
- Kimchigang.
- Yes.
I'll start with the...
And then you stir-fry,
but then you add also the kimchi.
Red chili paste.
Fish sauce.
I just need this much.
[Tamarind]
I know you guys are tired of sinigang.
- That's their secret, though.
- This one?
Add the eggplant.
It tastes like kimchi stew.
Yes!
Mmm, it's delicious.
That's how it should be.
Okay.
Done.
Done, done, done.
Kimchigang.
[Completed Kimchigang]
It's a little spicy 'cause of the kimchi.
Kimchinigang.
Kimchigang.
- Oh, it's kimchigang.
- Yes.
Thank you!
The flavor is very good.
The flavor is sour-spicy.
- Delicious.
- Thank you.
Wow!
- So, you added kimchi?
- Kimchi.
- It goes well, right?
- It does.
The flavor is like a hybrid.
A cross between Filipino cuisine
and Korean flavors.
Thank you.
We should've served this.
Don't, don't, don't.
I like it, though.
I like the spice.
While we're eating, would you like to...
- discuss as well?
- Yeah.
- We can still improve the ordering system.
- Correct.
The person taking the order
- needs to communicate with the kitchen.
- Right.
- Yes.
- So that's like,
"Okay, inasal for Table 1." "Okay, check."
So that we know...
- Just two voices.
- Yeah.
Yeah, but hey guys,
[Kumusta: Growing Pains]
these are called birth pains.
- Yeah.
- We can't solve everything.
So Arci's with you, just later.
Okay.
- She's gonna collapse.
- She's...
- Okay.
- Overfatigue.
You know what, it's fatigue.
So you deserve the rest.
I'll make it up to you guys tomorrow.
- I promise. I'm so sorry.
- Okay.
- Yeah, no worries.
- Don't say sorry.
Take the day off.
- Ah, thank you.
- Go home please.
Thank you.
[Francine Will Be Taking The Day Off]
Hey, help us out.
For the prep!
Okay!
No, not you. The camera.
- But she was ready to go like, "Okay!"
- We need you.
[5 Members During Lunch]
[4 Members For Dinner]
[Open]
We're open.
[30 mins to go]
Thirty minutes.
I am ready, once again. Let's go.
That squid, we need to slice it.
This one, because it's a...
Too big? Too long?
No, it's ugly now.
Ay, ugly.
Roughly chop.
Maybe I should fry them first.
- Okay.
- Because it might slip through the fryer.
You're smart.
Smart.
Okay, while I'm waiting,
I'm gonna put a fish in.
We serve the welcome drinks and the appetizer.
And then, this is the menu.
- That's how they are.
- Okay.
- Five and six, yes.
- Five, six.
- Seven, eight, nine.
- Nine.
Okay.
One, two, three, four...
[1 minute to go]
Opening in a minute.
[Ready]
- Ready?
- Yeah.
- Okay, so...
- One, two, three.
- You want to do?
- Fighting!
One, two, three!
Kumusta!
Fighting!
Alright.
Chef, good luck.
Good luck.
And werk it.
- What?
- And werk it.
What is that?
It's from Drag Race.
Philippines.
- Yeah, yeah. First day.
- Okay.
- Act professionally.
Oh, yeah.
[Open]
Yaayyy!
- Officially open. Let's go!
- Yes, let's go.
[Today's Menu: Sea Bream]
Kumusta.
- Now, we wait for our customers.
- Okay.
Are they coming? I'm nervous...
- Really?
- Yes.
- For me, the language...
- I'd rather cook.
Because I'm shy.
- Shy type.
I'll just drink water.
Okay, go.
Are you guys okay?
I'd rather cook.
- You need help?
- No.
Okay.
Sweetie?
Where's Mona?
Where's she?
Has anyone seen Mona?
Arci!
Mona!
Where's Mona?
- I don't know.
- She's in the bathroom.
Because I'm shy.
- Shy type.
Welcome!
- Hello!
- Hi!
For two?
Where do we seat them, Jodi?
- They can sit there.
- Okay.
Okay.
Please follow me.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you.
Have a seat.
Here it is.
[A Nervous Debut on the Floor]
Okay.
Okay, menu.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Your menu.
What should we eat?
I'll get the appetizers.
Ay, not yet.
- After they order.
- Okay.
So we are going to give them water first.
- Yes.
[Like a Baby Bird Following Its Mother]
Water?
Water.
- We'll come back once they're ready to order.
- Okay.
That's how it works.
Let's just wait.
Pork, pork meat.
I'm so nervous.
Okay.
- Shall we order Palabok?
- Yeah.
- Pork...
- Okay?
- They're ready. Oh, go.
- Yes.
Okay.
[The Baby Bird Leaves the Nest]
Yes, hello.
- Yes.
- Palabok, one.
Oh, palabok.
Yeah, palabok.
Palabok.
- One?
- Salt-crusted.
Okay. One.
Oh, okay.
Thank you.
Okay.
Jodi, table number...
- One, two, three.
- Three.
- Okay, order!
- Okay!
Okay, one palabok, one sea bream,
[Taking Her First Flight]
one garlic rice.
Okay!
Okay.
She's pretty strong.
- Here, yellow.
- There's still a lot of this.
- Okay?
- Okay. Alright.
[Before/After]
We can still improve the ordering system.
- Correct.
- Match it.
- Match it!
- One palabok, one fish,
[Do Not Forget!]
one garlic rice!
The sauce...
Here it is.
Here are your freebies.
Okay. Appetizer.
This is tofu adobo.
This is chicken skin.
Papaya salad, and anchovies.
Alright. Enjoy your meal.
- Shall we try?
- Tofu?
- Tofu, chicken skin.
- Skin.
Anchovies, papaya salad.
[100 Points]
[Perfectly Communicated]
- Your beer.
- Oh, are you feeling cold? Are you okay?
- No, I'm fine.
[Serving Kindness]
Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Beer.
[A Refreshing Start]
- Hi!
- Yes!
- Hello!
- Hello, welcome!
Have a seat.
Thank you.
- One garlic rice.
- Okay.
- And one inasal.
- One inasal.
Okay, got it.
One sea bream, one palabok,
- one beer, and one Sprite.
- Okay.
- Kitchen!
- Yes?
Order up!
We got one inasal, one garlic rice...
One sea bream, one palabok.
- Yes.
- I'll make the sauce first.
Okay.
Palabok sauce, okay.
Noodles.
Palabok noodles.
There we go.
We're just missing the egg.
- Palabok?
- Because of the eggs.
Oh, okay.
How's the egg? Is it cooked yet?
Ah, that's good to go!
But it's not boiling, though?
Yeah, but it'll be fine.
It's hot.
Look, it's fine.
So, just peel it.
- Okay. It's hot, right?
- So...
No, it's okay.
- Get a board.
- I rolled it and it...
Ah, okay. That's fine.
So, what happened...
- It's soft-boiled.
- What we can do is...
Throw that.
These eggs are not the best anymore.
Yeah, they're not.
- Kitchen!
- Isn't this okay already?
So, I need palabok.
I need...
Eggs. Sorry, we don't have eggs. Boiling.
Okay.
The palabok is taking too long.
This is not boiling, so I'll do...
- We can do...
- It's soft-boiled.
What we can do is...
Okay, let's just serve it without the egg.
- What?
How can you serve palabok without the egg?
It's like the heart of the palabok.
Consistency?
Yeah.
[Committed to a Perfect Palabok]
- Okay, we have to wait, though.
- Yeah.
- Boiling eggs, five minutes.
- For what?
- For the palabok.
The palabok is a blockbuster.
Alright, I like that you stand your ground.
Like when? The egg?
Yeah, I mean, some chefs...
There's a lot of "shortcut chefs."
So that's where sometimes a restaurant is good.
Quality control.
And like, you stand your ground.
"No, no, no. We shouldn't serve the..."
- If it's not tasty.
- Or without the egg.
- So, it can't be substandard.
- Yeah.
I think this is good to go.
I'll open one up.
It's okay?
Yeah, perfect.
Hey, can you get ready for...
Okay, so...
Let's just go with this.
This is okay for now.
Okay, palabok is ready for Table 3.
- Palabok.
- Table 3, okay.
Your palabok.
- Enjoy your meal!
- Thank you.
Should we try it out?
There's egg.
It looks delicious.
Ta-da!
Hi!
It's really delicious.
Okay, it's perfectly cooked.
I heard perfectly cooked, so ready to serve.
With fish, I have...
I cook fish pretty decently.
Okay.
Okay, I'll do the inasal next.
[Perfectly Cooked]
- Sea bream.
Hold on, I'll wipe it.
Tissue, tissue, tissue!
Yeah, perfect, then you're good.
[Perfectly Finished]
Okay.
Perfect.
Sea bream.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Papaya atchara.
Pickled papaya, anchovies, and mango jam.
- Mango jam.
- Ah, papaya.
With bean sprouts.
[Ha! Perfect!]
Ha! Perfect!
- Honey, try this.
- You can order it.
"Yeobo" is "honey."
- Honey.
Oh, it's delicious.
[Perfect Service]
Interesting flavor.
[Perfect Service, Peak Satisfaction]
Thank you.
Hi, guys!
Sorry to pressure you.
Okay.
So, can you repeat? What do I owe you?
Okay. One more fish.
- Yeah.
- One more palabok.
One inasal, please.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Chef, there's hair!
Ah, that's a leaf.
This is a leaf?
Okay.
Oh, right.
[Perfectionist]
Because I am a perfectionist.
I know.
Thank you so much for waiting.
This is inasal.
Garlic rice.
Enjoy your meal!
Okay, you need anything else?
- No.
- Okay.
- Thank you!
- Thank you.
Okay...
Oh, it's an outdoor table.
Can we sit anywhere?
- Excuse me!
- Oh, hi! Good evening!
- Welcome!
- Thank you.
- Hi! Hello! How are you?
- Hi!
- Hi! Come here!
- Where should we sit?
Follow me, please.
- Please have a seat.
- Okay.
Are you okay to sit here?
- Oh, yes.
- Should we sit here?
Or over here.
It's up to you,
where you feel most comfortable.
Here, okay. Please sit down.
I'll come back for the menu.
Okay, thank you.
You speak English very naturally.
Somehow, I managed to speak in English.
She's so pretty.
She has such a small face.
You know, foreigners usually have
very small faces.
- Hi!
- Here's your menu.
Hello!
Both of you are so pretty.
You look like dolls.
How do you have such small faces?
- What did they say?
- They said we have small faces.
You're so pretty as well!
- Jodi Sta. Maria?
- Yes.
- And Arci...
- ♪ Maria ♪
♪ Ave Maria ♪
- Good! Your voice is very good!
- Amazing!
We're singers.
- She said that we're both singers.
- Singers?
- Wow!
- Yeah.
She's a Korean singer
and I do, like, opera singing.
Wow!
Opera, and you do...
- Like Korean...
- Korean singer.
- It's called trot.
- Ballad.
- Trot?
- Trot.
It's like Korean folk song.
- That's so nice.
- Right.
- That's really hard.
- Yeah.
- But thank you so much for visiting us!
- You two are so pretty.
- Thank you.
- J.
- Yeah?
She's an opera singer.
- We have a guest.
- Opera? Oh, wow.
- Oh, Korean folk song, right?
- Folk song, yeah.
I want to hear you sing one day.
I want to learn about.
Give us a minute to decide.
- Of course. Yes, please go ahead.
- One minute.
- Thank you.
- Take your time.
Okay, so let's decide on our main dish.
Do you want chicken or fish?
What do you like?
It's my first time trying Filipino food.
I can't choose. I really can't.
It says this will be served
with vinegar and calamansi.
It's Filipino chicken. What do we do?
It's a bit unfamiliar.
Ah, okay.
Excuse me, hello.
Is everything okay?
What's good here?
- Can you give us some recommendations?
- This is inasal chicken.
Filipino style.
- Yes.
- Filipino style.
- This one is...
- This...
Filipino style glass noodles.
- Glass noodles!
- Yes.
So, it's like...
- Like noodle, noodle. Yes.
- I love glass noodles!
We have fish.
- Sea bream?
- Yes, but Filipino style.
Let's get sea bream,
and you pick from the top section.
- Okay.
- What's gising-gising?
Yeah, what's gising-gising?
- Vegetables with coconut milk.
- Gising-gising.
- Coconut!
- Yes.
- I love it!
- You do?
- You've got a thing for gising-gising, huh?
- Right.
- Thank you.
- Okay.
She's cute.
Okay, so you owe me one more fish.
- One more fish?
- One gising-gising.
- There's gising-gising?
- One palabok.
Okay.
Okay, this is for you.
These are our appetizers.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Thank you so much, and enjoy your appetizers.
- Oh, yes.
- Thank you.
It's my first time trying Filipino cuisine.
- Really?
- Ever.
- In your entire life?
- In my entire life.
Okay, I hope that we don't disappoint.
I don't think so.
- You okay, J?
- Yeah.
That's perfect.
Gising-gising...
It's okay. Gising-gising.
Palabok noodles ready.
There we go.
Okay.
Palabok and gising-gising.
Hello!
- So, this is your palabok.
- Is this glass noodles?
- Filipino glass noodles?
- Yes, similar to Korean glass noodles.
- It's palabok and... gising-gising.
- Gising-gising.
- Yeah.
- Gising-gising!
- Yes.
- I feel like I should take a picture.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
- Please enjoy.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
We really need to take a picture of this.
- It's so colorful.
- You're good at taking pictures, right?
Let's go!
I've never seen anything like this.
This is the gising-gising
that you've been looking forward to.
The flavor is amazing-mazing.
The shrimp is the key.
- It tastes like those shrimp crackers.
- Wow, it's so delicious.
Wow, this gising-gising
is gonna be hard to beat.
Right, I'll surely crave
this gising-gising again.
Filipino glass noodles, let's go!
Shrimp-based.
SB, SB.
It kind of tastes like curry, too.
These Filipino glass noodles
are totally my kind of food.
[Falling in Love 3]
[Falling in Love 2]
[Falling in Love 1]
I've fallen in love with Filipino food.
Hello!
Hi, table for how many?
- For two.
- Yeah, two.
- Is this okay?
- Yes.
- Here's the menu.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
The name is so cute.
Gising-gising!
Why aren't you looking at me?
Welcome!
Okay, for two.
- Okay.
- For two.
Okay, here you go.
Please have a seat.
Hello!
Okay.
Where's the palabok sauce?
- What?
- Where's the palabok sauce?
- Is this the one?
- Yeah.
Okay. One sinigang, one sea bream,
garlic rice, and one gising-gising.
- Where did it go?
- Thank you.
- Which one?
- The palabok sauce.
Oh, here! I'm blind.
Okay.
- Okay.
- What did she say?
Hold on.
- Did you hear what she said?
- No.
I did not hear anything.
Sorry.
Mon, Mon!
- Mon!
- Yes?
Service?
Can you...
- Okay, so...
- Tell us.
So over here, Table 4 is complete.
Table 1 is complete.
Table 8...
I need one more fish.
- One more fish?
- Yes.
Table 6, one sinigang, one more fish.
One garlic rice and one gising-gising.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Gising-gising is on the way.
So, gising-gising...
Gising-gising is ready.
This is gising-gising.
- Ah, gising-gising!
- Yes.
- Wake-wake.
- Wake-wake?
- Enjoy your meal!
- Thank you.
Okay.
What else, what else, what else?
Okay, so...
So, one sinigang.
Okay.
Sinigang ready.
Sinigang.
- Woah.
- Okay, I'll just get that.
Yes! Yes, yes.
- Yes?
- We're ready to order.
- One palabok.
- Okay.
One inasal.
Got it.
- I'd appreciate if you could make it quick.
- Quick? Of course!
Yes, of course. Right away.
Thank you. Okay.
Order's up, Table 5.
They are in a rush, so...
Oh God.
Oh dear...
- We've got a lot to do today, right?
- We do, actually.
Because they're going somewhere else.
And they want palabok and inasal.
Perfect, I've already got some palabok going.
Okay! Good, good, good.
- Palabok ready!
- Got it!
Okay. Here's your palabok.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
- It looks good.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
- I need my inasal.
- Inasal.
- I'll get on the chicken.
- I'll make it then.
Be good, be good, be good.
Alright.
- It's coming out.
- Alright.
Table 5, inasal.
- Ready to serve.
- Thank you.
- Here's your inasal.
Enjoy your meal!
Table 5, complete.
Okay, the service for Table 5
was really fast, good job.
Thank you.
Ah, can you put the sauce beside the fish?
Okay!
Okay, you can take it.
- Up and drizzle it with some love.
- Okay.
Okay.
- Have you worked in a restaurant before?
- Sorry?
Nope.
But I always watch.
Wow.
Here.
Thank you so much for waiting.
Here's your meal.
Wow, this looks amazing.
- The presentation is amazing.
- Yeah.
- Wow, no wonder it took so long.
- I know, right?
- They cooked an entire fish like this.
- Right.
- Enjoy your meal!
- It looks good.
- Okay.
- Thank you!
Oh, orders for those two tables
are already complete.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank God for Arci.
She's been so helpful.
- I wish she could work here for good.
- I know, right?
Yeah, she's amazing.
She is!
Super, super, super.
[Kumusta's MVP Arci Muñoz]
Enjoy your fish, sweetie.
Okay.
Drizzle it with some love.
Wow, this tastes amazing.
[Drizzle of Love Worked Its Magic]
This flavor is very familiar.
- Delicious.
- This is exactly my kind of thing.
[Stealing Hearts Left and Right]
It's really good.
The fish flavor is nice and clean.
Really?
Salt-grilled?
- Salt-grilled?
- Yes.
No, no!
- Why?
- I'll eat it myself.
- It has a bold flavor to it.
- It's bold?
Yes.
- Yes.
[Bolder?]
[Bolder? Than I Am?]
Bolder?
Wow.
[Sea Bream Over Husband!]
Okay.
Excuse me.
[Here Comes The Bias Wrecker]
- Shall we put this in the middle?
- Here's your meal.
Thank you.
Wow, this is so pretty.
- Enjoy your meal.
- It looks so good.
- Enjoy your meal. I hope you like it.
- Delicious!
- Delicious?
- Delicious.
[I Love Palabok]
Thank you.
- Enjoy. Okay.
- Thank you.
This is just... wow.
Woah!
[Still Hooked On The Palabok...]
There are some fish bones over there.
I'll turn this.
You know what, just dig into it.
Wow, this is amazing.
[Palabok is Her One and Only]
How can they grill the sea bream like this?
- Is it good?
- Yes.
I actually love sea bream.
It's delicious.
Wow, it's really fresh.
The sauce is a bit strong,
but this amount is fine.
[Palabok Who?]
Sea bream, sea bream.
Wow, this feels like a steak.
- Ah, on the skin.
- I've got it.
The skin is perfectly seasoned with salt.
Hello, ladies!
So how do you find your food?
You really love the sea bream, huh?
Yes!
This is... wow!
The size, we've never experienced this...
- This big?
- This big size of a fish.
It's so tasty and it's new,
but such a good experience.
- That's good to know.
- Yes.
How about the palabok and your gising-gising?
Ah, gising-gising...
It's the best?
Gising-gising was good.
How about the palabok and your gising-gising?
[How About You?]
[The Winner Is...]
Oh, this is my favorite.
- Because it's familiar.
- Is it like somewhat similar
to your glass noodles or different?
Ah, Korean style glass noodle.
But the sauce and the spice
are kind of different.
But I loved.
- You love it?
- Yeah.
It's good to know.
It's so tasty I think I fell in love
with Filipino food.
Oh, thank you.
I cannot wait to actually try it
in the Philippines.
I hope that one day,
you get to visit the country.
- Yeah.
- And you'll enjoy it more.
I think so.
Is the Philippines far away?
I'm actually not sure, I'll look it up.
It's my first time trying Filipino food
and it's actually good.
I think I was built for Filipino food.
Don't go to the Philippines.
Stay right by my side.
Don't go anywhere, honey.
[Love Blooms in Kumusta]
Hi, excuse me.
He's the chef.
- Chef JP.
- Hello, how are you guys?
- How's your food?
- Everything is so tasty.
- It's so great.
- Thank you.
It's my first time ever trying Filipino food.
- Yes.
- And you made such a good memory.
- Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
How do you find the flavors?
You know, it's very tasty and colorful.
And it has so many tastes.
So it reminds me...
It's unique.
Yeah, "unique," she said.
Never tasted. Something new to Korea.
- I see.
- Gising-gising.
Especially this one. She loves.
- Gising-gising?
- Yeah.
He wants you to try the inasal.
- This is on the house.
- Really?
- Oh, thank you!
- Yes.
- Do you have space for chicken?
- I'm...
- There's always space.
- Yes.
This is a specialty
from my hometown in the Philippines.
- Thank you.
- Try the chicken.
We...
- Seriously...
- We are eating like monsters!
I really wanted to try this.
Wow, that smell is...
Absolutely insane!
Imagine if I missed out!
How is the chicken, ladies?
- So good! Yes.
- Good?
- Absolutely perfect!
- We loved.
It was really good.
Thank you.
We were about to order
between chicken and fish.
But you read our minds.
Great, great, great.
- Thank you for today.
- Yay!
- Thank you for such delicious food.
- It's nothing.
Oh, Miss?
- Yes?
- Can we take pictures?
Oh yes! Sis!
Ah, okay!
Okay, okay.
One, two, three!
So pretty!
Thank you.
Thank you!
Please come visit us in the Philippines.
- We want to.
- Yeah.
- Really?
- Really.
A promise?
- A promise.
- Oh, "promise" it is.
Promise!
- Thank you!
Take care!
- Bye-bye!
- Take care!
- Thank you.
- Thank you!
- Bye.
- Good night!
- Thank you!
Thank you.
- Bye-bye!
- Bye!
I have to turn my stove off!
♪ Somewhere ♪
♪ Over ♪
This is so much fun!
♪ Some... ♪
Okay, no more people.
[Closed]
Guys, closing time!
♪ Closing time ♪
- Good job.
But I have to give you the credit, Mona.
It's as if you're running 10,000 restaurants.
- Yeah.
- You can handle it.
You know exactly what you're doing.
Thank you, Mona.
We are so blessed with your presence.
Thank you. I absolutely enjoyed...
your company.
I had no idea you could cook.
Ah, you... you can literally do everything.
Ah, as for you... you're on your own.
- Hey, I also need affirmation.
- Love you!
- Love you, Chef! Cheers!
- Just this one.
I was struggling, we're struggling together.
But we made it through!
Chef J, congratulations.
What you're doing in the kitchen
is definitely not a simple task.
You did a great job.
Thank you.
I might start crying.
It's true, you did amazing.
My gosh.
And I like it that you never give up.
You're always like,
"No, no, no, let me figure it out."
And then you're like, "I got this.
I have nothing to do anyways."
You're like, you have that attitude.
I know things are not easy, right?
- Things...
- But it was fast.
Yeah.
Chef, there's a mosquito!
Right when I'm about to cry...
- Jodi, why do you have friends like this?
- Oh my God.
Mona!
- Did you kill it?
- I can't...
You're driving me crazy!
Oh, my makeup...
- Cheers, big ears!
- Cheers!
Sorry, Chef.
He might've gotten bitten, so I had to...
Let's get a good rest.
Let's end the night with a positive note.
Everything is going to be fine.
[Day 3]
It's a new day.
- We're so glad you're back.
- Yes!
- Welcome back, Francine!
- I tried to...
save up my energy. Ay, sorry.
I'm glad you're better.
- I'm here. I'm back, guys.
- Happy.
I'll make it up to you guys.
- Okay.
- Hello!
- Oh my God!
- Oh my God.
- Nice to meet you.
Welcome, everyone!
- Hello!
- Come on in!
[1 Hour Ago]
Oh, here it is.
Do we have new staff?
[New Staff?]
[Epilogue]
This is Janella.
- Hi!
- Ah, yes. Chef Janella.
- Janella.
- Yes.
- Chef J.
- Wait, do you do music?
- Yes.
- She's a very good singer.
- Right!
- Yes!
- She's a rock star.
- She is Mulan of...
- Moana!
- Ay, Moana!
- ♪ Moana ♪
- In the Philippines.
- Really?
- Moana.
- You're a singer too?
- No!
- She has a band. She's a rock star.
- I'm not!
- No, it's true!
- But I'm...
I'm not a singer. I'm a rapper. Just kidding!
So that's what it was!
Let's just sing instead.
Sure.
Janella, show them what you've got!
You show them too!
- ♪ Janella ♪
- ♪ Moana ♪
- She's a rock star.
- I'm not!
[Rock Is My Life]
No, it's true!